Edwin Diamond Political Audiovisual Collection
Edwin Diamond Political Audiovisual Collection
- Tapes D0001-D0299
  - D0194 White Papers - If Japan Can Why Can't We? 1 of 2 - Producer: NBC, 6/12/80 (Box 12)
  - D0195 White Papers - If Japan Can Why Can't We? 2 of 2 - Producer: NBC, 7/28/80 (Box 12)
  - D0196 Today Show - Producer: NBC, 2/22/83 (Box 12)
  - D0197 Today - Producer: NBC, 2/25/83 (Box 12)
  - D0198 Media Series - Producer: NBC, 3/1/85 (Box 12)
  - D0199 Early Morning News - Producer: NBC, 3/30/83 (Box 12)
  - D0200 Overnight [?] - Producer: NBC, 5/12/83 (Box 12)
  - D0201 AIDS Segments - ONN & NN - Producer: NBC, 8/18/83 (Box 13)
  - D0202 Strictly Business (Press and Publicity), 09/29/85; diamond_e_015; compilation tape of shows 25, 27, 28, 30; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; running time 60:00 (Box 13)
  - D0203 NBC in Lebanon (November revision) - Producer: NBC (Box 13)
  - D0204 Mondale - Soviets - Bikini - Producer: NCTA, 6/4/84 (Box 13)
  - D0205 Babbitt, Robertson Campaign Ads - Producer: New York Magazine (Box 13)
  - D0206 Brown interview / Political spots '76 Carter, Reagan, Udall... - Producer: Newsmakers KNXT, 5/30/76 (Box 13)
  - D0207 Japanese news - Producer: NHK (Box 13)
  - D0208 Convention - Sloan Funded - Producer: NSG, 1976 (Box 13)
  - D0209 Conferencia Genebra JN - Producer: NTV, 3/11 - 12/?? (Box 13)
  - D0210 Jill Leger / Gregg Geller - Producer: NYU - TV, 2/22/96 (Box 13)
  - D0211 Hershey - "News Reel" - Producer: Ogilvy and Mather (Box 13)
  - D0212 Tina w/ Anchalee, Tina w/Evandro, Generic Tina - Producer: Ogilvy and Mather (Box 13)
  - D0213 Something Fishy at City Hall - Murdered Sentenced/SOC - Coronary bypass - Part 2 of 3 part series - School Bus Cops - Noon News Block Live Remote Report - Producer: Patricia VanHecke (Box 13)
  - D0214 Dukakis for President - Producer: Payne and Company (Box 13)
  - D0215 How Much is Enough: Decision Making in the Nuclear Age - Andy Stern - Producer: PBS (Box 13)
  - D0216 Air Force One: The Planes and the Presidents - Producer: PBS - Elliott Sluhan Productions, 11/15/84 (Box 13)
  - D0217 Bill Shanley Dub - Rush to Judgment - Producer: PBS (Box 13)
  - D0218 - Producer: People for the American Way (Box 14)
  - D0219 Diet Pepsi / Mustang w/ Top Gun - Producer: Pepsi Cola Company, 2/23/87 (Box 14)
  - D0220 PTL Club (1st hour) - Producer: PTL - TV, 3/1/79 (Box 14)
  - D0221 Presentation Reel - PBS Vers. - Producer: Public Affairs Television, 4/10/87 (Box 14)
  - D0222 The Street - Episode #13 - "Cold Hands" - Producer: Quantum Media, 3/17/88 (Box 14)
  - D0223 Wisk, Hellman's Mayonnaise, Underalls, Hanes - Producer: Radio TV Reports Inc. (Box 14)
  - D0224 David Bowie - Ashes to Ashes - Producer: RCA Records (Box 14)
  - D0225 David Bowie - The Lodger - Producer: RCA Records (Box 14)
  - D0226 David Bowie - Fashion - Producer: RCA Records (Box 14)
  - D0227 Russia Alt. End - Producer: RCC Co. (Box 14)
  - D0228 Choice - Producer: Republican National Committee Records (Box 14)
  - D0229 National ads - Producer: RNC, 1982 (Box 14)
  - D0230 TV Broadcast Work - What You Look At / Three Part Work / 51% / 2 min Broadcast - Producer: Robert Briggs (Box 14)
  - D0231 Harlequin Books - Superromance/Horse - Producer: Rosenfeld, Sirowitz & Lawson, 5/26/82 (Box 14)
  - D0232 Floyd Haskel - A Senator for the People - Producer: Rothstien Buckley (Box 14)
  - D0233 Floyd Haskel - Spots 1 - 5 - Producer: Rothstien Buckley (Box 14)
  - D0234 Pataki for Governor - Taxed Everything, Long Island Thirty, Property Taxes - NY - Producer: Russo, Marsh & Associates, 10/10/94 (Box 15)
  - D0235 Ghost - David - Cyra Hunter - Producer: San Francisco Examiner, 11/21/85 (Box 15)
  - D0236 8 - 9PM - Producer: Satellite News Channel, 3/11/83 (Box 15)
  - D0237 Energy in the Eighties - Producer: Science TV News (Box 15)
  - D0238 Physics in Medicine - Producer: Science TV News (Box 15)
  - D0239 Astronomy News - Producer: Science TV News (Box 15)
  - D0240 The Gospel According to Television - Producer: Scripps - Howard Broadcasting Company (Box 15)
  - D0241 Ads - 39 spots - Various Companies - Producer: Sedelmaier, 10/28/83 (Box 15)
  - D0242 Ads - Various Companies - Producer: Sedelmaier, 1/17/84 (Box 15)
  - D0243 125 Hour Day / March Lyric Blocks - Producer: Showtime, 2/24/82 (Box 15)
  - D0244 Reagan - Bush '84 Spots - Producer: The President's Authorized Campaign Committee, 3/1/84 (Box 15)
  - D0245 Bill Moyers Journal - A Reporter's Notebook - Producer: Thirteen, 2/17/80 (Box 15)
  - D0246 Non Fiction TV: On Company Business - Producer: Thirteen, 4/22/80 (Box 15)
  - D0247 Political Commercials - Producer: Thirteen, 4/23/80 (Box 15)
  - D0248 Pope Spot - Producer: Tony Schwartz (Box 15)
  - D0249 The Cajuns - Producer: TVTV (Box 15)
  - D0250 David Frost Interviews Richard Nixon Tape #2 - Producer: WBZ TV, 5/4 - 12/77 (Box 15)
  - D0251 David Frost Interviews Richard Nixon Tape #3 - Producer: WBZ - TV, 5/12/77 (Box 16)
  - D0252 Dan Rea - MIT News Study Group Study of Political Ads - Producer: WBZ - TV, 4/10/80 (Box 16)
  - D0253 Chuck Kraemer piece - Sarcastic Review of Mayor White's Campaign Ads - Producer: WCVB - TV, 1979 (Box 16)
  - D0254 Ed Diamond Commentary - Producer: WDVM, 10/4/78 (Box 16)
  - D0255 New York Magazine Reel - Ellen Burkeman - Producer: Wells, Rich, Greene, 11/17/86 (Box 16)
  - D0256 Maidas Int'l - Freedom of Choice - Producer: Wells, Rich, Greene (Box 16)
  - D0257 Edwin Diamond an Busing Coverage - Print Media News - Producer: WGBH TV, 9/10 - 11/75 (Box 16)
  - D0258 The Kennedy - Nixon Debates 1960 - Tape 2 - Producer: WGBH, 9/20/76 (Box 16)
  - D0259 USA: People and Politics - Producer: WGBH, 10/29/76 (Box 16)
  - D0260 MASS Senatorial Debate - Producer: WGBH / WTEV, 10/31/76 (Box 16)
  - D0261 World - Blacks Britannica - Koff Version - Producer: WGBH, 8/12/78 (Box 16)
  - D0262 World - F - 16: Sale of the Century - Producer: WGBH (Box 16)
  - D0263 World - Italy: Chain Reaction - Producer: WGBH (Box 16)
  - D0264 World - The Islamic Bomb - Producer: WGBH (Box 16)
  - D0265 Mike Dukakis: The First 100 Days - Producer: WGBH (Box 16)
  - D0266 World - Australia: The Lucky Country? - Producer: WGBH (Box 17)
  - D0267 Nova - A Normal Face - #1020 - Producer: WGBH (Box 17)
  - D0268 The Word is Out: Documentary on Gays - Part I - Producer: WGBH (Box 17)
  - D0269 The Word is Out: Documentary on Gays - Part II - Producer: WGBH (Box 17)
  - D0270 World - The Chinese Way: Agriculture in the People's Republic of China - Producer: WGBH (Box 17)
  - D0271 World - Soviet TV: Heroes, Workers and the Party Line - Producer: WGBH, 7/10 - 12/85 (Box 17)
  - D0272 Eyewitness 11PM News - Producer: WJXT - Jacksonville, FL, 9/1/76 (Box 17)
  - D0273 Eyewitness 11PM News - Producer: WJXT - Jacksonville, FL, 11/15/76 (Box 17)
  - D0274 Special Report on AIDS - Producer: WNBC, 10/25/85 (Box 17)
  - D0275 Rolanda Watts Report on AIDS - Producer: WNBC, 10/25/85 (Box 17)
  - D0276 Ed Diamond - Adweeks Best and Worst Ads of the Year - Today 12/9/?? - Producer: WNBC (Box 17)
  - D0277 Today - Ed Diamond Adweek's Best and Worst Ads 12/9/?? - Producer: WNBC (Box 17)
  - D0278 City Edition #140 - Producer: WNET, 3/6/80 (Box 17)
  - D0279 NH 1984 Democratic Presidential Primary Debate - Phil Donahue moderates - #4 - Producer: WNEV - TV, 11/15/84 (Box 17)
  - D0280 If Japan Can Why Can't We? White Papers - 1 of 2 - Producer: Working Paper Productions, 7/28/80 (3/5/81) (Box 17)
  - D0281 If Japan Can Why Can't We? White Papers - 2 of 2 - Producer: Working Paper Productions (Box 17)
  - D0282 Bogota (Colombia) - Producer: World (Box 17)
  - D0283 Cuban Sports - Producer: World (Box 18)
  - D0284 The Nguba Connection: Peanuts Around the World: Their Economic and Political Implications Particularly with US & West Africa - Producer: World (Box 18)
  - D0285 Selling of Abe Lincoln - Producer: WTTW (Box 18)
  - D0286 Steampipe Alley #9 Easter Show - Producer: WWOR - TV (Box 18)
  - D0287 The Streets Slaes Tapes - Producer: WWOR - TV (Box 18)
  - D0288 Robert Able & Assoc. TRW - "Changing Pictures" - Producer: WYSE Advertising, 12/13/82 (Box 18)
  - D0289 Awards Winners of the 1984 Cannes International Advertising Film Festival - Producer: Young & Rubicam, 9/24/84 (Box 18)
  - D0290 O'Toole Political Spots '60 - '72, 1960 - 1972 (Box 18)
  - D0291 Kanter Collection Political Spots, 5/2/68 (Box 18)
  - D0292 A Conversation with the President - Ford, 8/7/75 (Box 18)
  - D0293 Busing Media Coverage, 9/8/75 (Box 18)
  - D0294 Busing Media Coverage, 9/8/75 (Box 18)
  - D0295 Busing Media Coverage, 9/8/75 (Box 18)
  - D0296 Busing Media Coverage, 9/8/75 (Box 18)
  - D0297 Busing Media Coverage, 9/8/75 (Box 18)
  - D0298 Busing Media Coverage, 9/8/75 (Box 19)
  - D0299 Busing Media Coverage, 9/8/75 (Box 19)
- Tapes D0300-D0599
  - D0300 Busing Media Coverage, 9/8/75 (Box 19)
  - D0301 Busing Media Coverage, 9/8/75 (Box 19)
  - D0302 2d Ford Carter Debate / There is no Soviet Domination of Eastern Europe, 10/6/75 (Box 19)
  - D0303 Father Michael Groden / Outside Milk St. (blue) / Outside 100 Cambridge St. (Murray's), 11/12/75; case has different info. (Box 19)
  - D0304 NYC Local News Part 1 5 - 6PM, 11/18/75 (Box 19)
  - D0305 Press Watch 1976 / Politics and TV - Process in Action (Box 19)
  - D0306 Political Spot Collection Old Spots, Ford Carter '76 Hatch (MA), Tsongas - Brooke '78, 1976 - 1978 (Box 19)
  - D0307 Carter Spot for NY Primary, 4/7/76 (Box 19)
  - D0308 Political Commercials - San Diego 1 of 2, 6/1/76 (Box 19)
  - D0309 Reagan Show / Ford - Reagan Ads / PBS Programs on Candidates / Political Spots (Box 19)
  - D0310 Pre Election Coverage - Election Day Coverage - NJ Primary Election - Night Coverage & Political Spots, 6/7/76 (Box 19)
  - D0311 Busing Media Coverage, 9/10/76 (Box 19)
  - D0312 The First Ford - Carter Debate - 1st hour, 9/23/76 (Box 19)
  - D0313 The First Ford - Carter Debate - last 1/2 hour, plus delay / Ch. 5 Report from MIT, 9/23/76 (Box 19)
  - D0314 The Non Voting American, 10/1/76 (Box 20)
  - D0315 Campaign '76 show reel, 11/4/76 (Box 20)
  - D0316 National Women's Conference Coverage, 1977 (Box 20)
  - D0317 Carter Press Conference (alter 1st energy speech), 4/22/77 (Box 20)
  - D0318 Political Spots - Brooke / Brooke - Tsongas Debate, 1978 (Box 20)
  - D0319 NJ Nightly News Cassette II, 1978 (Box 20)
  - D0320 New Jersey Nightly News, 1978 (Box 20)
  - D0321 Dick Flavin Dubs Political Comedy, 5/12/78 (Box 20)
  - D0322 Election Eve Roundup 1978 (Presidential Hopefuls), 10/5/78 (Box 20)
  - D0323 Brooke - Tsongas Debate #2 - Staring Ed Diamond, 10/31/78 (Box 20)
  - D0324 Victor Livingston Video News Reports, 1979 (Box 20)
  - D0325 Dick Flavin Dubs II, 1/17 - 24/79; 2/6 - 14/79 (Box 20)
  - D0326 Bill Moyers Journal: Out of the Reach of Children - Children Targeted Advertising, 4/12/79 (Box 20)
  - D0327 Bill Moyers Journal: A Conversation with Jerry Brown, 4/25/79 (Box 20)
  - D0328 Interview with Henry Kissinger by David Frost, 10/11/79 (Box 20)
  - D0329 Ted Turner Interview, 11/01/1979; diamond_e_014; Turner only, opening w/cw.; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; running time 20:00 (Box 20)
  - D0330 Television News Shows Limitations to Change, 12/1/79 (Box 20)
  - D0331 Ed Clark's Spot CBS News Special Report, Hostages, Iran's Arms and War, Commercial, Iran's Demands - Assets, Commercial, Campaign '80, Commercial, 1980 (Box 21)
  - D0332 Reagan - Carter Debate / Also Cable News Questions John Anderson, 1980 (Box 21)
  - D0333 Anderson Campaigns in Stamford - Baby Rescued, 1980 (Box 21)
  - D0334 Republican Presidential Debate - 1 of 3, 1/5/80 (Box 21)
  - D0335 Republican Presidential Debate - 2 of 3, 1/5/80 (Box 21)
  - D0336 Republican Presidential Debate - 3 of 3, 1/5/80 (Box 21)
  - D0337 Interface Kennedy Speech - David Sawyer / Herrea '78 / Carey '78, 1/9/80 (Box 21)
  - D0338 Mobil Composite - Earnings for 1979, 1/23/80 (Box 21)
  - D0339 Political Commercials for all Candidates, 2/5 - 23/80 (Box 21)
  - D0340 Jerry Brown 1/2 hour Political Spot - Part II, 2/22/80 (Box 21)
  - D0341 Jerry Brown 1/2 hour Political Spot - Part 1, 2/22/80 (Box 21)
  - D0342 Carter Press Conference - Part 1, 2/29/80 (Box 21)
  - D0343 Carter Press Conference - Part II, 2/29/80 (Box 21)
  - D0344 News Study Group with Andy Hiller / Frank Mankelwisz, 4/13/80 (Box 21)
  - D0346 Dan Rather at Harvard - Afghanistan & the Media, 5/9/80 (Box 21)
  - D0347 Data Spot, Newscast, 5/9/80 (Box 21)
  - D0348 Coverage of Exit Polling, 11/4/80 (Box 21)
  - D0349 Calvin Klein Jeans Ads, 1981 (Box 21)
  - D0350 Dub. Eurikon '82 (Box 21)
  - D0351 Hartford Courant Northeast Presentation - Multi Media, 1/1/82 (Box 22)
  - D0352 Focus on Advertising - Edwin Diamond, 4/19/82 (Box 22)
  - D0353 Brodnox [?] Fenway, 8/25/82 (Box 22)
  - D0354 Massachusetts and New Hampshire Political Ads, 10/1/82 (Box 22)
  - D0355 Some Portion of Dukakis/Sears Debate, 10/23/82 (Box 22)
  - D0356 Kennedy/Shamie - US Senate Debate, 10/24/82 (Box 22)
  - D0357 Ed Diamond Commentary - Dubs, 11/26/82; 1/21/83 (Box 22)
  - D0358 Ed Diamond - Globe, 12/3/82 (Box 22)
  - D0359 Late Nite News, 12/8/82 (Box 22)
  - D0360 Late Night News, 12/9/82 (Box 22)
  - D0361 The Nightly Business Report, 11/5/83 (Box 22)
  - D0362 Ken Swope - Demo Reel, 3/18/83 (Box 22)
  - D0363 Hitler Diary Commentary, 4/21/83 (Box 22)
  - D0364 9 Fiurregan Spots, 10/3/83 (Box 22)
  - D0365 America Remembers JFK, 10/29/83 (Box 22)
  - D0366 Cannes '84 #2 - Set III, 1984 (Box 22)
  - D0367 New Hampshire Debate - Tape #2 (Box 23)
  - D0368 Phil Donahue Moderates - #3, 11/15/84 (Box 23)
  - D0369 Cranston, McGovern, 2/84 (Box 23)
  - D0370 Political Ads 1952-84 - Greatest Hits, 5/7/84 (Box 23)
  - D0371 60 Min Vol XVII No. 20 "Mali" (Box 23)
  - D0372 Warren Franke - Heart Problems, 2/11/85 (Box 23)
  - D0373 2 Stories from Barry Cornet (possibly Eating Cell 2), 6/24/86 (Box 23)
  - D0374 The Best of WRG, 6/24/86 (Box 23)
  - D0375 Bernice Kanner NY Magazine interview reel -, 9/23/86 (Box 23)
  - D0376 Jack Kemp Presidential Campaign, 1/17/87 (Box 23)
  - D0377 48 Hours In the Cocaine War, 4/28/88 (Box 23)
  - D0378 3rd Ford/Carter Debate Tape 2, 10/22/?? (Box 23)
  - D0379 Hemingway - St. Marks Pl.: A Documentary (Box 23)
  - D0380 TV on Trial (Box 23)
  - D0381 70th Anniversary (Box 23)
  - D0382 Hour of Power w/ Robert Schulter (Box 23)
  - D0383 Oral Roberts Show - 3 Excerpts (Box 23)
  - D0384 Pete Wilson for Senate / c - 303 Overspending /F4RF Friends (Revised) (Box 24)
  - D0385 Glenn "A New America" / Hubert Humphrey anti - Nixon / Kennedy (Box 24)
  - D0386 Clyde See for Governor, Bio Spot 101 (Box 24)
  - D0387 New Mexico Symphony... [rest of label illegible] (Box 24)
  - D0388 First Strike (Box 24)
  - D0389 The Global Consequences of Nuclear War (Box 24)
  - D0390 John Rhodes - Wm. Patterson College (Box 24)
  - D0391 Impact: Housing (Box 24)
  - D0392 Nuclear Power - Connecticut & Pennsylvania - Excerpt from News Programs (Box 24)
  - D0393 1980 - to date: American Made for Cinema (Box 24)
  - D0394 Television Vietnam: The Impact of Media (Box 24)
  - D0395 Max Headroom - A History, Your Interview, Coca Cola Advertising and Promotional Material (Box 24)
  - D0396 Kidworld - Pilot - Children's News Program - Features (Box 24)
  - D0397 Warren Franke, Harold Herold (Box 24)
  - D0398 Various Flavins (Box 24)
  - D0399 Tapes of Wrath (Box 24)
  - D0400 Peanuts to President - The Carter Campaign Part I (Box 25)
  - D0401 Ads - Various Companies (Box 25)
  - D0402 Watching the Watch Dog (Box 25)
  - D0403 Deardorf Ford Ads (Box 25)
  - D0404 Revlon, Charlie - 'Mother Thinks' Ad / Aviance Advertising for Women Series / Senchal Life - Ads to Women / Epton Spots Gospel TV (Box 25)
  - D0405 Gospel TV (Box 25)
  - D0406 Peanuts to President - The Carter Campaign Part II (Box 25)
  - D0407 John Connally - 1 hour Political Spot (Box 25)
  - D0408 The Best of Nixon - Checkers Speech, Nixon/Kennedy Debate/ Resignation (Box 25)
  - D0409 One World - New York (Box 25)
  - D0410 Ed Diamond an City Edition "Air Wars" - inc. Daisy (Box 25)
  - D0411 Pre - Election Night Spots - McCarthy, Carter, Ford (Box 25)
  - D0412 Bush Spots - Family/Children, The Future, I am That Man, The Mission (Box 25)
  - D0413 Campaign Spots - Presidential George Bush / Mayoral Tom Bradley, Ed Koch (Box 25)
  - D0414 Till Death Do Us Part - Producer: 48 Hours, 2/6/91 (Box 25)
    VHS
  - D0415 Whose Side Are You On? Mike Wallace - Producer: 48 Hours, 5/17/91 (Box 25)
  - D0416 Return to Crack Street - Producer: 48 Hours, 6/21/90 (Box 25)
  - D0417 Trump & Merr - Producer: 60 Minutes (Box 25)
  - D0418 Multimedia Learning - Presentation Tape - Producer: AA Media (Box 25)
  - D0419 News JFK / News KFC of JFK - Producer: ABC (Box 25)
  - D0420 LWV Debates - Producer: ABC/WNT, 10/8 - 22/84 (Box 25)
  - D0421 Rambo Mania - Producer: ABC, 7/17/85 (Box 26)
  - D0422 Diamond on ABC Weekend / Jeff Greenfield Picture Week - Producer: ABC, 9/13/85 (Box 26)
  - D0423 Summit Coverage: Nightline, Worldnews - Producer: ABC, 10/1 - 4/85 (Box 26)
  - D0424 Moscow Summit - Nightly - Producer: ABC, 5/30 - 6/1/88 (Box 26)
  - D0425 Moscow Summit 1988 - Producer: ABC, 5/31 - 6/2/88 (Box 26)
  - D0426 Morning News - Producer: ABC, 6/1/88 (Box 26)
  - D0427 Morning News - Producer: ABC, 6/2/88 (Box 26)
  - D0428 Emperor's Passing - Producer: ABC/CBS/PBS, 1/6/89 (Box 26)
  - D0429 Primetime Live - White House Broadcast - Producer: ABC, 9/21/89 (Box 26)
  - D0430 Prime Time - Producer: ABC, 10/19/89 (Box 26)
  - D0431 Prime Time - David Duke / Who Owns America / Nicaragua / Carly Simon - Producer: ABC, 11/6/89 (Box 26)
  - D0432 Primetime Live: East Germany / Supreme Soviet - Producer: ABC, 1/6/89 (Box 26)
  - D0433 Prague / Rome / Malta Anchors Aweigh - Producer: ABC / CBS / NBC, 11/27/89 (Box 26)
  - D0434 News - Nightline History - Producer: ABC, 2/25/92 (Box 26)
  - D0435 News - World News Now - Producer: ABC, 3/27/92 (Box 26)
  - D0436 News - Primetime Live - Floyd Brown Spot - Producer: ABC, 10/22/92 (Box 26)
  - D0437 News - Nightline - 72 Hours to Victory: Behind the Scenes with Bill Clinton - Producer: ABC, 11/4/92 (Box 26)
  - D0438 News - The Great Health Care Debate - Producer: ABC, 11/5/93 (Box 26)
  - D0439 News - Special Report - Saturday/Sunday - Producer: ABC, 2/5 - 6/94 (Box 26)
  - D0440 News - WNT - Whitewater - Producer: ABC, 2/9/94 (Box 26)
  - D0441 Bush Prime Time Press Conference and Post Commentary - Producer: ABC/CBS/NBC, 6/8 - 25/?? (Box 26)
  - D0442 Stations plus CNN Press Conference audio only - Producer: ABC/CBS/NBC, 6/23 - 23/?? (Box 26)
  - D0443 Local News Specials - Producer: ABC/CBS, 7/17/?? (Box 26)
  - D0444 Evening News - Producer: ABC, 11/4 - 8/?? (Box 26)
  - D0445 Eve News - Producer: ABC, 11/7 - 20/?? (Box 26)
  - D0446 Summit 1985 Eve News Reagan Summit Speed and Commentary - Producer: ABC/CBS, 11/21 - 22/?? (Box 26)
  - D0447 Hostages - Producer: ABC (Box 26)
  - D0448 World News Tonite with Peter Jennings - Producer: ABC (Box 26)
  - D0449 Mr. Clean For Us - Producer: Abrams for Senate, 2 Copies (Box 26)
  - D0450 Issue #5: Marketing High - Tech - Producer: Ad Video Journal (Box 26)
  - D0451 AIDS Changing the Rules - Producer: AIDS Films, 7/27/87 (Box 26)
  - D0452 AIDS Changing the Rules Final Version - Producer: AIDS Films, 7/27/87 (Box 26)
  - D0453 Lamar! Come on Along! - Producer: Alexander for President Inc (Box 26)
  - D0454 Show 1 - Network vs. Cable News / Show 2 - Tabloid vs. Hard News Shows / Show 3 - News Ethics - Producer: All About TV, 12/15/92 (Box 26)
  - D0455 Shows #1500 - 1502 guest copy - Producer: All About TV (Box 26)
  - D0456 Video Trial Report - California v. Powell: A Defense Against a Videotape - Producer: American Lawyer/Court TV, The, 6/1/92 (Box 26)
  - D0457 The Technological Underpinnings of Telecommunications Policy: The Technologies of Common Carrier - Producer: Annenberg Washington Program, The, 1995; 4 Tapes (Box 26)
  - D0458 The Fight Goes On - Producer: Anti Defamation League, 1992 (Box 26)
  - D0459 Presidential Campaign Commercials - Round 1 - Producer: Aristotle Industries, 1986 (Box 26)
  - D0460 A Perfect Candidate by R.J. Cutter & David VanTaylor - Producer: Arpie Films (Box 26)
  - D0461 The Life & Loves of a She Devil - Producer: Arts & Entertainment, 5/18/87 (Box 26)
  - D0462 Nippon: Being Japanese - Producer: Arts & Entertainment, 1/30/91 (Box 26)
  - D0463 Nippon: The Shock Effect - Producer: Arts & Entertainment, 1/30/91 (Box 26)
  - D0464 Nippon: Risen Sun - Producer: Arts & Entertainment, 1/30/91 (Box 26)
  - D0465 As it Happened: The Great Debates - Producer: Arts & Entertainment (Box 27)
  - D0466 The JFK Assassination: As it Happened - Producer: Art s & Entertainment, 1st 40 Minutes (Box 27)
  - D0467 California Spots - General Election 1986 - Producer: B. Surman, 11/4/86 (Box 27)
  - D0468 Hot Cooler - Producer: Bartles & Jaymes (Box 27)
  - D0469 Seminar #4 - Youth Programming: Turning on the Twenty Somethings - Producer: BBC, 2/11/91 (Box 27)
  - D0470 Divided We Stand - Viewing Tape - Producer: BBC, 11/23/95 (Box 27)
  - D0471 Later...with Bob Costas - Producer: Betelgeuse Productions (Box 27)
  - D0472 Edwin Diamond - "Behind the Times" - interview - Producer: Bloomberg Forum, 1/26/94 (Box 27)
  - D0473 Edwin Diamond - "Behind the Times" - Interview - Producer: Bloomberg Forum, 1/26/94 (Box 27)
  - D0474 The Bakery Centre - Producer: Broadcast Quality Inc. (Box 27)
  - D0475 Take Back America - Producer: Brown for President, 1/22/92 (Box 27)
  - D0476 False - Producer: Bush / Quayle '92, 2/28/92 (Box 27)
  - D0477 See Spot Run 1992 - Producer: Campaign Magazine, 3/2/92 (Box 27)
  - D0478 National Security PAC "Weekend Passes" - Producer: Campaign Magazine (Box 27)
  - D0479 Ross Perot - Producer: Campaign Magazine Video Series (Box 27)
  - D0480 Special Request Collection of Campaign Commercials - Producer: Campaign Magazine Video Series (Box 27)
  - D0481 Tropicana Orange Juice - Bruce Jenner's Orange Grove / Wendy's - Frozen Hamburgers - Producer: CBS / ABC, 2/28/83 (Box 27)
  - D0482 TV Guide - Producer: CBS (Box 27)
  - D0483 News - Nightwatch - Allyn Conwell Interview - Producer: CBS (Box 27)
  - D0484 West 57: Show #1 - Producer: CBS, 8/8/85 (Box 27)
  - D0485 Evening News - Producer: CBS, 10/14 - 17/85 (Box 27)
  - D0486 National News - News Study Group - Producer: CBS, 11/4 - 6/85 (Box 27)
  - D0487 News - AM Shows - Producer: CBS, 11/18 - 19/85 (Box 27)
  - D0488 News - News Study Group AM Only - Producer: CBS, 11/20/85 (Box 27)
  - D0489 60 Minutes - Hansenfus - Producer: CBS (Box 27)
  - D0490 48 Hours: Televangelists - Producer: CBS (Box 27)
  - D0491 Morning News - Producer: CBS, 5/27/88 (Box 27)
  - D0492 Moscow Summit 1988 / McNeil - Lehrer - Producer: CBS/PBS, 5/31 - 6/2/88 (Box 27)
  - D0493 Morning News - Producer: CBS, 6/1/88 (Box 27)
  - D0494 Morning News - Producer: CBS, 6/2/88 (Box 27)
  - D0495 48 Hours - China Rebellion - Producer: CBS, 5/18/89 (Box 27)
  - D0496 Through the Wall - Berlin - Producer: CBS, 11/9/89 (Box 27)
  - D0497 Reports - D - Day Screening Copy - Producer: CBS, 5/26/94 (Box 27)
  - D0498 Reports - When American Trembled...Murrow/McCarthy - Producer: CBS (Box 27)
  - D0499 Nightly News - Producer: CBS/NBC, 6/14 - 16/??, 6/26/?? (Box 27)
  - D0500 Evening News - Summit - Reagan's Address to Congress - Producer: CBS, 11/13 - 22/?? (Box 27)
  - D0501 News Study Group CBS AM & PM - Producer: CBS, 11/19/?? (Box 27)
  - D0502 AM & PM - Producer: CBS, 11/22/?? (Box 27)
  - D0503 CNN Project - News Study Group - CBS News - Producer: CBS/CNN, 11/20 - 21/?? (Box 27)
  - D0504 Robert Silverman [?] - Producer: CBS (Box 27)
  - D0505 TV Guide Project + Maureen Reagan - ET / Hart / Ferraro / 60 min. Bradley - Producer: CBS (Box 27)
  - D0506 Iacocca, RR Announces, Iowa Primary '84, News Reel Moyers - Producer: CBS/NBC (Box 27)